DEASIA LITTLE

SYSTEMS INTEGRATION AND TEST ENGINEER

CONTACT ☐ 678-458-7063 ☑ deasialittle@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/deasia-little SKILLS Manual Testing Selenium JIRA Linux Python C++ Java MySQL HTML C#

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Tuskegee University

2013-2017

- · Graduated Magna Cum Laude
- · Vice president of Upsilon Pi Epsilon
- One of three students at the university to receive the Monsanto Fund 1890s Student Scholarship
- Represented the university at the Black Enterprise Tech ConneXt Summit hackathon in 2016

PROFILE

Dedicated and experienced test engineer with extensive knowledge in manual and automated testing. Adept in maximizing efficiency of the testing cycle, troubleshooting, and working to offer solutions. Substantial experience in very thorough analysis during the testing process to ensure zero to minimum escapes for software releases

WORK EXPERIENCE

System Integration and Test Engineer

L3Harris Technologies

2019-Current

- Spearheaded testing for a web application and radio integration program, achieving a 90% reduction in post-release defects.
- Monitored daily system health, resolving issues related to database replication, storage space, and system outages proactively.
- Installed software for internal releases, contributing to improvements in release stability through rigorous verification.
- Recorded and tracked test cases and defects in Jira, resulting in a 30% increase in communication efficiency within the development team.
- Conducted a 100% comprehensive regression testing on existing system features, ensuring a robust and error-free application.
- Collaborated in customer installations, resolving 95% of real-time installation errors, enhancing customer satisfaction.
- Maintained and expanded the automated test suite, adding 10% more test cases using the Page Object Model design pattern.

Software Engineer

L3Harris Technologies

2017-2019

- Developed and maintained robust software solutions, contributing to a 20% reduction in system bugs and enhancing overall system stability.
- Collaborated in the design, implementation, testing, and debugging of complex software systems, ensuring alignment with technical and customer requirements.
- Conducted and actively participated in over 15 code and design reviews, successfully identifying and resolving issues, resulting in a 30% decrease in post-release defects.
- Achieved \$20,000 in salary savings and a 500-hour reduction in development time through efficient bug elimination during code and design reviews.

Software Engineer Intern

L3Harris Technologies

2016-2016

- Develop scripts that are compatible with over 24,000 Android devices that activate phone calls and manipulate cellular technology
- Create manuals and scripts to utilize Sierra Wireless AirPrime modules for testing, saving the company \$1700 against similar products
- Install operating systems on computers saving \$19,000 per year in salary distribution